http://www.fantasyguru.com/privacy-policy

Skip to primary navigation Skip to main contentDaily Fantasy Seasonal Fantasy FanLink Sports
winning with an edge
GURU FANTASY REPORTS, INC. PRIVACY POLICY
Last updated: 12/11/19
Guru Fantasy
Reports, Inc. (“Guru Fantasy Reports,”
“we,” “us,” or “our”) owns and
operates its fantasy sports websites located at FantasyGuru.com,
EliteFantasy.com, and EliteSportsBetting.com and related applications, content,
products, tools, features, subscriptions, and services (collectively, the “Services”). PLEASE READ OUR TERMS OF SERVICE FOR DETAILED
INFORMATION ABOUT OUR SERVICES AND YOUR LEGAL OBLIGATIONS.
This
Privacy Policy (the “Policy”) is intended to provide information on how
we collect, process, and share your personal data. Personal data – or personal
information – is any information that relates to you – an identified or
identifiable natural person.   When we use the terms “you” or
“your” in this Policy, we are referring to individuals who access or use
our Services in any way.
Our Services are available only to residents of the
United States and Canada who are 18 years of age or older.  If you are located outside the US or Canada, you
are prohibited from registering for an account or accessing the Services in any
way.
After reading this Policy, if you have additional questions or would like further information, please contact us at support@fantasyguru.com.
PERSONAL
DATA WE COLLECT AND HOW WE USE IT
As
further explained below, we collect and process your personal data only for
lawful reasons, such as our legitimate business interests, your consent, or to
fulfill our legal or contractual obligations.
Information You Provide to Us When you use our Services, we may ask you to provide certain personal data. Depending on the activity you are attempting to complete, this may include any of the following:
NameUsernameEmail addressAddress, city,
state/province, country, zipCredit card or other
payment informationYour companyProfile pictureAny other personal
information you provide to us at your option, including in articles, comments, chat
rooms, or other online communication forums
We use the data you provide to set up your account, provide the Services, and communicate with you.  We also may use your contact information to periodically send promotional emails about new products, special offers, or other information which we think you may find interesting using the information that you have provided.  You are always able to opt-out of these marketing communications by contacting us at support@fantasyguru.com
or clicking the “unsubscribe” link in the communication.
Usage Information
We may collect, use, and/or store certain standard web measurements and tracking technologies, such as “cookies,” web server logs, or other statistics programs to collect usage information, track and record how you use our Services, and coordinate services with our partners and affiliates.  Guru Fantasy Reports and its analytics partners use cookies and similar technologies to provide, market, and improve the Services, including to keep track of your preferences and profile information, customize services and content, measure promotional effectiveness, and to secure your accounts.  You have options to control or limit how we or our partners use cookies and similar technologies.  For more information, please see www.allaboutcookies.org/cookies.
Third Party Advertising
We may use
third-party advertising companies and/or media partners to serve ads on our Services
and/or on other websites on which we advertise. Please note that these
companies may use usage information about your visit to our Services, or other
sites in accordance with the policies on those sites, in order to provide
advertisements about goods and services that may be of interest to you. We may
use usage information and compile aggregate data about it in order to improve
our Services, target the advertising, and assess the general effectiveness of
such advertising.
Third parties may also place cookies or other tracking technologies to collect information about your use of the Services. We also allow other third parties (e.g., ad networks and ad servers) to serve tailored ads to you on the Services, and to access their own cookies or other tracking technologies device you use to access the Services.  If you wish to opt out of interest-based advertising, click here. Please note, you will continue to receive generic ads.
HOW
WE SHARE YOUR INFORMATION
When we share your
information with third parties, we do so lawfully and only to provide the
Services or for other legitimate business or legal purposes as described below:
We may share your
information with our service providers, partners, sponsors, or affiliates in
order to provide the Services, communicate with you, and store your data.We may disclose your information
in response to any subpoenas, court orders, or other legal process we receive,
or to establish or exercise our legal rights or to defend against legal claims.We may share your
information with third-party analytics or advertising partners.We may disclose your
information when we believe it appropriate in order to investigate, prevent, or
take action regarding possible illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations
involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of
the Terms of Service for the Services you accessed, and/or to protect our
rights and property.
As we continue to
develop our business, we may sell, buy, or partner with other companies or
businesses. In such event, we may transfer or assign the information we have
collected as part of such merger, acquisition, sale, or other change of
control. In such transactions, your personal data may be among the transferred
assets.
Also, in the
unlikely event of our bankruptcy, insolvency, reorganization, receivership, or
assignment for the benefit of creditors, or the application of laws or
equitable principles affecting creditors’ rights generally, we may not be able
to control how your personal data is treated, transferred, or used and your personal
data may be included in the transferred assets.
Credit Card/Payment Information
If you are
purchasing our Services, you may be asked to provide credit card or other
payment information. In such event, it is our policy to redirect you to a
payment processing portal hosted by a third-party payment processor.  We do not collect, access, store, or process
any credit card or payment information. Please see our
payment processor’s privacy policy regarding the use, storage, and
protection of your credit card information before submitting any credit card
information.
ONLINE CHAT ROOMS,FORUMS, ARTICLES, AND COMMENTS
We make chat rooms,
articles, and similar content areas available for public comments and discussions
with other users. Your username and profile picture will be visible to other
users and potentially the public when you use our chat rooms and content areas.  We cannot control the information that is
shared by other users.
Please remember that
any information you voluntarily post in our chat rooms, content areas,
comments, or any public area of the internet may be viewable by other members
or the public at large . Please exercise caution when deciding to post your views
and personal data via our Services.
You will not be able to remove your content after you have posted it.  Our administrators may delete or modify your posts in their sole discretion.  If you have an issue with any posts, you may contact support@fantasyguru.com.
HOW WE PROTECT YOUR DATA
We are committed
to ensuring that your information is secure. We have implemented commercially
reasonable technical measures to protect against the risks of unauthorized
access to, erroneous disclosure of, and unlawful interception of personal data submitted
via our Services or otherwise collected or possessed by us.
While
we take reasonable precautions against possible security breaches, no website
or internet transmission is completely secure and we cannot guarantee that
unauthorized access, hacking, data loss or other breach will never occur. In
the event that any information under our control is compromised as a result of
a breach of security, we will take reasonable steps to investigate the
situation and where appropriate, notify those individuals whose information may
have been compromised and take other steps, in accordance with any applicable
laws and regulations.
INTERNATIONAL
TRANSFERS
We
currently do not intentionally accept users from outside the United States or
Canada, and we will take reasonable steps to delete any data we receive from
outside those countries. If you provide us data from outside the United States,
it will necessarily be transferred to the United States for processing and
storage, and by using the Services, you consent to such transfer.
THIRD PARTY LINKS
Our Services may
contain links to other websites, which may have privacy policies that differ
from our own. We are also not responsible for any information or content
contained on such sites. Your browsing, use, and interaction on any other
websites, including websites which have a link to our Services, are subject to
that third-party website’s own rules and policies. Please review the privacy
policy posted on any website that you may access through, or which links to, our
Services.
CHILDREN
Our Services are not intended for children under 18 years of age.  Do not sign up with our Services or send us any information if you are under 18 years of age.  If you believe we have collected any personal information from a child younger than 13 years of age, please notify us immediately at support@fantasyguru.com.
ACCESS,
MODIFY, AND DELETE YOUR DATA
Subject to the limitations discussed above regarding chat rooms, articles, and other content areas, you may have the right to request access to your data or to modify or delete your data.  Please make such requests at support@fantasyguru.com.
CONTACT US
If you have any questions regarding this information or our privacy practices, or if you wish to make a complaint, email us at support@fantasyguru.com, or write to us at:
Guru Fantasy Reports, Inc.401 Park Avenue South10th FloorNew York, NY 10016  Thank you for visiting our site!
Top
